<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<stratfile>
	<dateCreated>20111109T17:40:45-0800</dateCreated>
	<dateLastAccessed>20130326T21:35:55-0700</dateLastAccessed>
	<dateModified>20130326T19:44:09-0700</dateModified>
	<permissions>0600</permissions>
	<model>StratPad 1.5 (959)</model>
	<email>hotyogamel@mac.com</email>
	<name>Mantra Yoga Carlsbad</name>
	<companyName>Mantra Yoga &amp; Juice</companyName>
	<city>San Diego</city>
	<provinceState>CA</provinceState>
	<country>USA</country>
	<industry>Health and Wellness</industry>
	<keyProblems>Why should I Practice yoga? 

People come to yoga for many reasons. Whether you are interested in physical fitness, healing chronic injuries, or experiencing inner peace, yoga has something to offer you. It is a fully integrated mind-body technique that is proven in numerous scientific studies to lower your level of stress, while increasing your sense of health and happiness. If you are interested in working with the quality of your mind, a regular yoga practice is the perfect place to practice mental clarity. By synchronizing the breathe, body and mind, a dedicated practitioner begins to experience deep and lasting transformation.

What about pre-existing pain and old injuries?

While you might feel sore or tired after doing your yoga practice or sometimes even during your yoga practice, it is not necessary to push your body to point of creating an injury. Throughout our lives we primarily tell our body what to do. With time, the yoga practice becomes an opportunity to listen to and respect what your body wants to tell you and do with you. In the advent of an injury, whether related to yoga or past outside experience, there are many special adjustments, modifications and considerations that one of our qualified teachers can advise you of. One of the main benefits of the yoga practice that you will experience over time is healing. By creating and inviting more balance into your overall state of being, a regular yoga practitioner creates the space to allow healing into their body on multiple levels.

I’m not flexible, can I still do yoga?
At Mantra Yoga, we welcome all type of bodies. Yoga is a physical exercise that will help increase your flexibility over time. You do not need to be flexible when you start yoga, however, over time you will see your range of flexibility increase. Over time, the regular and consistent practice of yoga will instill a balance between both strength and flexibility.
</keyProblems>
	<addressProblems>A style for every body...No one is too old to practice yoga. Pattabhi Jois, the living master of Ashtanga Yoga is 90 years old. There have been people who practice yoga and start at all ages and process of varying degrees of proficiency. The key to practicing yoga is not age, but rather an open mind and heart.


Class Styles

At Mantra Yoga Center you will find classes for all levels. We offer a variety of yoga instruction to facilitate your inner exploration. Our teachers provide thorough, educated, playful and empathic insight into your body, mind and deeper consciousness. Our classes give you a unique taste of yoga’s gift of peace, joy and health. Our classes draw upon the rich lineage of different styles and include a variety of Vinyasa classes as well. 

Mantra Yoga Flow TM 

This practice includes ancient breathing, asana, mantras, relaxation and meditation techniques that are practiced to remove negative states of mind, promoting positive thinking, leading to higher states of physical and mental health.
These specific practices are based on gaining true power founded in Self-knowledge and are initiated by sitting with the teacher and with continued self-practice to present a complete holistic system that creates stability in body, mind and spirit.
The emphasis of Mantra Yoga practice is for the student to develop their own way – a perfect path of yoga.

Mantra Candlelight TM

This class is taught with candlelight, music, and minimal instruction. It’s taught in a follow-the-leader format where the teacher practices alongside the class, encouraging students to let go of what the poses look like and focus on how the pose feels.

Mantra Hot Yoga 
It is important to note that “hot” in our style is a noun rather than an adjective, meaning that you can’t just turn up the heat in a room and do any style of yoga and call it Hot Yoga. Hot Yoga includes a distinct and therapeutic sequence of postures practiced in a heated room. It is considered a stationary sequence which means you come back to a stationary standing posture, Mountain Pose, between other postures. The stationary quality is ideal for beginners and advanced students. The focus is on building a solid foundation and understanding the principles of body alignment

Mantra Hot Vinyasa 
Vinyasa Yoga, also known as Flow Yoga, is a class of continuous movement where you flow from each posture. You synchronize the breath with every movement dictating the length of time held in the posture. Hot Vinyasa is like Hot Yoga in that it is taught with a therapeutic sequence to the postures. The class builds in succession, one posture preparing the body for the next. The flow is defined by the Sun Salutation, a series of six poses that creates the foundation of the class. The continuous movement of Hot Vinyasa makes this style more aerobic and more challenging than Hot Yoga. This class deepens the foundation and principles of alignment taught in the Hot Yoga sequence.


Reiki
Reiki is a Japanese technique for stress reduction and relaxation that also promotes healing. It is a form of hands-on-healing used to cleanse, balance and heal while invigorating the mind, body and soul. Reiki is based on the idea that an energy life force flows within each of us. 
The Healing Benefits of Reiki Include
Promotes Deep Relaxation
Improves Physical Health
Facilitates Metal Clarity
Clears Blockages and Aids Detoxification

Gentle Therapeutics Yoga
Restorative Yoga, known also as Gentle Therapeutics Yoga, is the yoga of non-doing and the core practice underlying the essence of all yoga. Even those with an active dynamic practice will benefit greatly from the inner peace and deep release of this restorative class. It is the practice of entering into Yoga postures using an assortment of props: blankets, bolsters, blocks, straps, walls, chairs, eye pillows etc. Supported and stabilized by various props, one experiences the yoga postures as profoundly relaxing and deeply rejuvenating, invoking a natural state of healing rest, renewal and equanimity. Supported and passive yoga postures allow the body to naturally release, letting go of held tension and stress. The results are a balanced state of being from inside out. A restorative class is a life enhancing practice and is appropriate for anyone at any age or stage of life and in any physical condition.

Guided Ashtanga: Full Primary
When you’re ready for the full Ashtanga experience, this is the class for you. In a fast-paced, dynamic sequence that opens new dimensions of the mind-body-breathe connection, you will begin to move into a direct experience of the flow of the practice. With careful emphasis on the traditional vinyasa method, this class presents the full Ashtanga Yoga Primary series. It is taught only by people who are qualified and will keep the integrity and purity of the practice. Prior yoga experience and proficiency or a high level of athletic conditioning recommended. Be prepared to sweat.

Kundalini  yoga uses breath, yogic postures and meditation to help maintain a healthy spine helping to strengthen the nervous and glandular systems. Each class can help one become aware of much more than just the strength of the body. It helps to facilitate a change physically as well as emotionally and spiritually. Kundalini yoga is yoga for the mind, body, and spirit.

.



</addressProblems>
	<customersDescription>In the Beautiful Oasis of sunny Carlsbad, California Mantra Yoga is a retreat space dedicated to the study of yoga, holistic health and consciousness is the ideal place to share a sense of your life’s purpose and meaning. Joining our community ensures your access to daily yoga classes, world class life coaching,nutrition counseling and gifted healers as well as workshops, trainings and special events with international leaders in yoga and spirituality. More holistic than a “yoga only” center, we offer you the possibility of real transformation and inspiration for your daily life.

At Mantra Yoga &amp; Juice you will find the perfect yoga class for your level, choose from Intro to Yoga Courses ideal for Beginners, Guided Ashtanga, Hot Yoga, Restorative, Power Yoga and Kundalini, Maintaining our standard of excellence, all of our Mantra Yoga teachers have been trained by masters of many different yoga traditions. We will be offering two Mantra yoga Teacher Trainings , a series of classes aimed at taking you through a deep learning and personal growth experience in yoga and life. Classes come straight from the source and are an authentic taste of the search for peace and balance that is the heart of yoga. 

Mantra Yoga provides a transformational learning and growth environments for individuals seeking to deepen their personal yoga practice, alongside with those who are walking the teachers and leaders path.

Through our immersion programs, you will gain profound knowledge and tools that empower you as you dive into asana, meditation, practice teaching, and self inquiry specifically designed to access your full potential. Mantra yoga will be known for their powerful teaching, authentic expression, commitment to empowering and transforming others, and fostering dynamic communities.

As yoga teacher or student of Mantra Yoga programs, it provide a deep and diversified learning environment in which to connect with your true self, ignite your growing edge, and create connections with a global community of people committed to living real, authentic lives through the methodology of Mantra Yoga 

At Mantra Yoga you can choose from a number of classes that speak to the many dimensions of experiences and living yoga. An invitation for you to explore our ever-expanding program offerings, and ask yourself what’s next for you, what program will inspire your fullest expression of life?

</customersDescription>
	<competitorsDescription>“Branding a yoga studio is like creating a mission statement about what you are offering to the community, and what makes you unique.”

In the last few years there has been an explosion of yoga studios opening across the country. These fledgling studios are a response to yoga’s surging popularity, with millions of people hitting the mat, according to USA Today. Yoga might be booming, but so is competition as eager yoga entrepreneurs saturate the market and divide the pie for student acquisition.

 There are many different business models for running a successful yoga studio. You can run a one person show, form a partnership with several yoga teachers, go in with only business experience, start a nonprofit, open a franchise like Bikram, or offer a multidestination studio that includes body care, food and a retail outlet.

Word of mouth is the best form of advertising, cite rent as their highest business expense, offer lucrative teacher training programs, and aren’t threatened by competition from other yoga studios or gym yoga classes.

Ironically the most effective way to get new clients is through recommendations from current clients, say studio owners. Because it encourages the formation of community, yoga in particular lends itself to the word of mouth, grass roots method of initiating new clients.

“I’ve spent two years experimenting with advertising and I’ve found it works well if you are selling yoga vacations or teacher training, but for filling classes, word of mouth is the far superior method,” says James Burkhart, sole instructor and owner of Soma Yoga.

How then do new or struggling studios encourage word of mouth? By giving their current clients the best yoga experience, atmosphere and customer service they can. Taking good care of current clients, focusing on good teaching and community building will inevitably lead to a buzz of word of mouth advertising, say most studio owners. 

The competition from other yoga studios or gym yoga isn't a threat. It seems that every time another yoga studio opens or a gym starts offering yoga, a studio get busier” The mainstream popularity of yoga as a boom for business. As people discover yoga at their gym or neighborhood yoga studios, they become hooked and eventually look to branch out to different styles or studios.  The effort to build community among clientele is the foundation of success. Mantra will begin with students introducing themselves to the people next to them.

For owners of new studios, who have yet to build a community of students, other streams of income may be necessary to keep the business initially afloat. Aaron Goldberg’s studio in Arizona, Inner Vision Yoga, is greatly subsidized by its teacher training programs. While he and his partners teach all the classes, bypassing the cost of paying teachers, overhead such as steep rent and restocking the on-site shop puts financial pressure on the studio. Teacher training helps assuage those costs by providing an income potential of $25,000 every three to four months. “In my opinion you are not going to get very far running a yoga studio without offering teacher training,” he adds.

Mantra yoga will offer Lifestyle enhancing programs, Teacher Trainings and weekly seminars.

Twenty-year veteran business coach Alón Sagee has been helping yoga entrepreneurs start and bolster their yoga businesses. According to him the secret of successful yoga studios lies in their ability to brand themselves. Proper branding eliminates the pressures of competition as each yoga studio creates its unique market niche. 

Branding a yoga studio is like creating a mission statement about what you are offering to the community and what makes you unique. This mission statement not only clearly communicates to the student the benefits of the yoga style offered but also the meaning that those benefits will have in the student’s life.

Mantra Yoga is unique niche is an all encompassing  style yoga studio that is also a multi-purpose destination and have a juice after a wonderful class. The body's internal system is a hardworking machine and just like us, it needs a break from time to time. That's where Mantras Juice raw, cold-pressed, organic juices come in handy. Packed with alkalizing and enzymatically active greens, roots, fruits, and herbs, Mantra juice will deliver your body the nutrition it needs without the chore of breaking it down. This allows the digestive system to rest and repair while old toxins are escorted out of the tissues and eliminated from the body. Did we mention this whole process is enjoyable too? Our unique certified organic blends combine the most delicious flavors to make the experience a treat from start to finish!

&quot;It is the kind of place where you can spend the day. You can take a yoga class, have a juice and do some shopping. 

Opening a yoga studio, like any new business, lends itself to making mistakes through the learning curves, but as long as the business vision and branding are clear, there is a solid foundation and any mistakes can be overcome. 

Competition isn’t really an issue in running a yoga studio because there is a huge market available for growth in the yoga community. The secret is to figure out what unique gift you have to offer the world, put it out there and the people who are meant to will find you






</competitorsDescription>
	<businessModelDescription>
Brand new Beginner class 

YOGA FOR BEGINNERS

Adding Mantra Yoga to your life can make a significant impact on your overall health. To begin you may choose to start with a one-hour hot class or perhaps participate in Mantra Yoga Introductory Challenge which includes up to 12 classes in 30 days and our Posture Clinics.

The Hot Yoga Posture Clinic and Hot Vinyasa Posture Clinic’s teach the basics of Hot Yoga and Vinyasa including: breathing techniques, standing and floor series poses, with a gradual introduction to heat. This course is an excellent way to discover our classes and how your body moves.

Are you interested in yoga?
- Do you want to enhance your energy, spirit and well-being?
- Are you uncertain where to begin?

Then this course is perfect for you! Our highly qualified instructors will give you a thorough, fun and down to earth introduction to yoga. You will learn everything you need to know to feel comfortable to attend yoga classes. Welcome yourself to this nurturing and inspirational beginning to your yoga journey.
Sign up today to reserve your spot. Space is limited.
Intro to Yoga
Mantra Yoga Introduction to Yoga Challenge yourself to one month of Yoga with up to 12 classes for only $59.00. Expiration Date: 1 month from first use $59.00

4 Week Course
Dates to be announced 

10 classes for 10 dollars 1 month expiration! The best and sweetest yoga deal in town, one month to use from first date you start. First timers only! 


Drop-In Yoga Class

$17

8-Class Level 1 Intro Series

$88 ($11/class)
INTRO Package includes:
8-Class Intro Series

$169 with Manduka Pro Lite Mat
Or 
$158 with Jade-Harmony Mat

KID YOGA ( coming soon) 
8-class, 8-week package
$88

5 Classes -expires in 60 days

$75 ($15/class)

10 Classes -expires in 120 days

20 Classes -expires in 180 days
$125 ($12.50/class)

$235 ($11.75/class)
One Month Unlimited
expires in 30 days

$130

Three Month Unlimited
expires in 90 days

$360 ($120/month)

Automatic Monthly Debit
(one year contract)

$100/month

Annual Unlimited Yoga Membership
(12 months)

$1200

Private Yoga Instruction
with Mantra instructor of your choice

$75 for 60 minutes
$110 for 90 minutes
$ 250 for Melissa :) 

Manduka Yoga Mat Rental( maybe) 

$2

Towel Rental

$2

Water Bottles

$1

Mantra Juice 
Beet Aid 
Mantra: Beet to rhythm of your own drum

$9.00 
Beet, Lime, Cucumber, Ginger 
Blood Building, Kidney Flushing, Stamina Creating

California Sunny Day 
Mantra &amp; Irish Blessing:  Let the long time shine upon you, let all love surround you, and the pure brilliance within you, guide your way on. 
$9.00 
Mixed Citrus
Cell Defending, Alkalizing, Bone Strengthening

Green God &amp; Goddess
Mantra: The power is within you, The &quot;super hero&quot; power is within us. 
$9.00 
Kale, Dandelion, Parsley, Spinach, Celery, lime 
Alkalizing, Healing, Stimulating, Mood Lifting

Hari Narayan has an important meaning. There is always a power within you. Because we are ruled by our mind, we don’t believe we have great power inside us. We think, ‘I don’t know I have this power’. We also believe, ‘I am not powerful’, even if others say that. Why? Because, we are in darkness as we are ruled by our mind. This mantra activates that supernatural power inside us.:) 


The real thirst quencher 
Mantra: Shine from the inside out
Cucumber, pineapple &amp; jalapeño
$9.00 
Cucumber, Pineapple, Jalapeño
Live Bromelain, Enzyme Power, Anti-inflammitory, Metabolism Boosting
Like Gatorade but without all the ick. 

Peppermint Patty 
Mantra: Life is Beautiful, Today I am open to a Miracle. 
12$ 
Greens, Maca, Mesquite, Mint Extract, Cacao Nibs, Almond Milk, Stevia or Coconut Nectar

Teacher Trainings and workshops 



</businessModelDescription>
	<expansionOptionsDescription>Mantra yoga online store and Yoga downloads. 500 hour yoga Teacher Training immersion would be the first in Carlsbad, California. 
Mantra Yoga clothing line. A Pay pal source to buy products, Trainings, services online. </expansionOptionsDescription>
	<ultimateAspiration>To be the most innovative Yoga studio on the West Coast leading Teacher Trainings that provide growth, Love, happiness and freedom in the hearts of all people who walk through Mantras doors. </ultimateAspiration>
	<mediumTermStrategicGoal>Within 6 months of opening we will offer the first 500 hr Teacher Training in Carlsbad, California.
The first Yoga/ Juice Bar. </mediumTermStrategicGoal>
	<themes>
		<theme>
			<title>Expand facility  and add new equipment </title>
			<startDate>20120929</startDate>
			<endDate>20130101</endDate>
			<mandatory>1</mandatory>
			<order>1</order>
			<enhanceCustomerValue>1</enhanceCustomerValue>
			<enhanceUniqueness>1</enhanceUniqueness>
			<expensesOneTime />
			<expensesMonthly />
			<expensesQuarterly />
			<expensesAnnually />
			<revenueMonthly>60000</revenueMonthly>
			<revenueOneTime />
			<revenueQuarterly />
			<revenueAnnually />
			<cogsOneTime />
			<cogsMonthly />
			<cogsQuarterly />
			<cogsAnnually />
			<costsOneTime />
			<costsMonthly>35000</costsMonthly>
			<costsQuarterly />
			<costsAnnually />
			<expensesMonthlyAdjustment />
			<expensesQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<expensesAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<revenueMonthlyAdjustment />
			<revenueQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<revenueAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<cogsMonthlyAdjustment />
			<cogsQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<cogsAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<costsMonthlyAdjustment />
			<costsQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<costsAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<responsible>Tom Russell &amp; Melissa Smith </responsible>
			<objectives>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Implement new CRM software</summary>
					<objectiveType>2</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>1</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>CRM software implemented</summary>
							<targetDate>20120331</targetDate>
							<targetValue />
							<successIndicator />
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities>
						<activity>
							<action>Untitled Activity</action>
							<startDate />
							<endDate>20120331</endDate>
							<upfrontCost />
							<ongoingCost />
							<order>0</order>
							<ongoingFrequency>3</ongoingFrequency>
							<responsible>Melissa Smith</responsible>
						</activity>
					</activities>
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Kickstart revenue</summary>
					<objectiveType>0</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>1</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Cumulative revenue</summary>
							<targetDate>20120930</targetDate>
							<targetValue>480000</targetValue>
							<successIndicator />
							<measurements>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120229</date>
									<value>6000</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120331</date>
									<value>15000</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120430</date>
									<value>27000</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120531</date>
									<value>42000</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120630</date>
									<value>73000</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
							</measurements>
							<charts>
								<chart>
									<title>Cumulative Revenue Chart</title>
									<zLayer>0</zLayer>
									<chartType>2</chartType>
									<showTrend>0</showTrend>
									<colorScheme>2</colorScheme>
									<showTarget>1</showTarget>
									<order>0</order>
									<uuid>AF1401F2-335D-45CD-B112-8B656C918098</uuid>
									<overlay />
									<yAxisMax />
								</chart>
								<chart>
									<title />
									<zLayer>1</zLayer>
									<chartType>1</chartType>
									<showTrend>0</showTrend>
									<colorScheme>3</colorScheme>
									<showTarget>0</showTarget>
									<order />
									<uuid>602F3A0A-7895-424B-BF09-F04ADF81024D</uuid>
									<overlay />
									<yAxisMax />
								</chart>
							</charts>
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities>
						<activity>
							<action>Take inventory of how many people are in classes</action>
							<startDate>20121231</startDate>
							<endDate>20130101</endDate>
							<upfrontCost>2000</upfrontCost>
							<ongoingCost>35</ongoingCost>
							<order>0</order>
							<ongoingFrequency>4</ongoingFrequency>
							<responsible>Melissa Smith</responsible>
						</activity>
					</activities>
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>1</order>
					<summary>Untitled Objective</summary>
					<objectiveType>0</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>3</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary />
							<targetDate />
							<targetValue />
							<successIndicator>0</successIndicator>
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities />
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>1</order>
					<summary>Expand and open another studio </summary>
					<objectiveType>1</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>1</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary />
							<targetDate />
							<targetValue />
							<successIndicator>0</successIndicator>
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities />
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>1</order>
					<summary>Train sales staff</summary>
					<objectiveType>3</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>3</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Trained staff</summary>
							<targetDate>20120331</targetDate>
							<targetValue />
							<successIndicator />
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities>
						<activity>
							<action>Train sales support staff</action>
							<startDate>20120301</startDate>
							<endDate>20120331</endDate>
							<upfrontCost />
							<ongoingCost />
							<order>0</order>
							<ongoingFrequency>3</ongoingFrequency>
							<responsible>Tom Russell &amp; Melissa Smith </responsible>
						</activity>
					</activities>
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Add sales support staff</summary>
					<objectiveType>3</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>1</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Sales support staff added</summary>
							<targetDate>20120229</targetDate>
							<targetValue />
							<successIndicator />
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities>
						<activity>
							<action>Hire sales support staff</action>
							<startDate>20120201</startDate>
							<endDate>20120229</endDate>
							<upfrontCost />
							<ongoingCost />
							<order>0</order>
							<ongoingFrequency>4</ongoingFrequency>
							<responsible>Tom Russell &amp; Melissa Smith </responsible>
						</activity>
					</activities>
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Connect with potential new customers</summary>
					<objectiveType>1</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>1</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Number of new contacts made</summary>
							<targetDate>20120630</targetDate>
							<targetValue>2500</targetValue>
							<successIndicator />
							<measurements>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120215</date>
									<value>375</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120229</date>
									<value>659</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120315</date>
									<value>1055</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120331</date>
									<value>1869</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120415</date>
									<value>2867</value>
									<comment>Incredible! We blew past our goal!</comment>
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120430</date>
									<value>3281</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120515</date>
									<value>4611</value>
									<comment>Number of potential prospects threatening to outstrip our ability to meet demand...</comment>
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120531</date>
									<value>5365</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120615</date>
									<value>6389</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
								<measurement>
									<date>20120630</date>
									<value>7890</value>
									<comment />
								</measurement>
							</measurements>
							<charts>
								<chart>
									<title>Number of new contacts w/ narrative</title>
									<zLayer>0</zLayer>
									<chartType>3</chartType>
									<showTrend>0</showTrend>
									<colorScheme>4</colorScheme>
									<showTarget>1</showTarget>
									<order>1</order>
									<uuid>AB03DC9F-A5D1-4C7C-95B0-E765FE4940EF</uuid>
									<overlay>BA4735DD-A506-4208-ACFB-F2464CFA2B15</overlay>
									<yAxisMax />
								</chart>
								<chart>
									<title>Number of new contacts and revenue</title>
									<zLayer>0</zLayer>
									<chartType>3</chartType>
									<showTrend>0</showTrend>
									<colorScheme>7</colorScheme>
									<showTarget>1</showTarget>
									<order>0</order>
									<uuid>1646D2FC-C385-4779-BEDF-ABC0E15BEA0C</uuid>
									<overlay>602F3A0A-7895-424B-BF09-F04ADF81024D</overlay>
									<yAxisMax />
								</chart>
								<chart>
									<title />
									<zLayer>1</zLayer>
									<chartType>4</chartType>
									<showTrend />
									<colorScheme>2</colorScheme>
									<showTarget />
									<order />
									<uuid>BA4735DD-A506-4208-ACFB-F2464CFA2B15</uuid>
									<overlay />
									<yAxisMax />
								</chart>
							</charts>
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities>
						<activity>
							<action>Implement out-bound marketing campaign</action>
							<startDate>20120401</startDate>
							<endDate>20120630</endDate>
							<upfrontCost>15000</upfrontCost>
							<ongoingCost>35</ongoingCost>
							<order>0</order>
							<ongoingFrequency>4</ongoingFrequency>
							<responsible>Tom Russell </responsible>
						</activity>
					</activities>
				</objective>
			</objectives>
		</theme>
		<theme>
			<title>Increase Marketing </title>
			<startDate>20120301</startDate>
			<endDate>20120930</endDate>
			<mandatory>1</mandatory>
			<order>2</order>
			<enhanceCustomerValue>1</enhanceCustomerValue>
			<enhanceUniqueness>1</enhanceUniqueness>
			<expensesOneTime />
			<expensesMonthly />
			<expensesQuarterly />
			<expensesAnnually />
			<revenueMonthly />
			<revenueOneTime />
			<revenueQuarterly />
			<revenueAnnually />
			<cogsOneTime />
			<cogsMonthly />
			<cogsQuarterly />
			<cogsAnnually />
			<costsOneTime />
			<costsMonthly>15000</costsMonthly>
			<costsQuarterly />
			<costsAnnually />
			<expensesMonthlyAdjustment />
			<expensesQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<expensesAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<revenueMonthlyAdjustment />
			<revenueQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<revenueAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<cogsMonthlyAdjustment />
			<cogsQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<cogsAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<costsMonthlyAdjustment />
			<costsQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<costsAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<responsible>Tom Russell &amp; Melissa Smith </responsible>
			<objectives>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Add reseller support staff</summary>
					<objectiveType>3</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>3</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Reseller support staff hired</summary>
							<targetDate>20120801</targetDate>
							<targetValue>1</targetValue>
							<successIndicator />
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities>
						<activity>
							<action>Add reseller support staff</action>
							<startDate>20120601</startDate>
							<endDate>20120630</endDate>
							<upfrontCost />
							<ongoingCost />
							<order>0</order>
							<ongoingFrequency>3</ongoingFrequency>
							<responsible>Melissa Smith</responsible>
						</activity>
						<activity>
							<action>Train reseller support staff</action>
							<startDate>20120701</startDate>
							<endDate>20120731</endDate>
							<upfrontCost />
							<ongoingCost />
							<order>1</order>
							<ongoingFrequency>3</ongoingFrequency>
							<responsible>Melissa Smith</responsible>
						</activity>
					</activities>
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Increase potential customers</summary>
					<objectiveType>1</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>3</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Number of prospective customers</summary>
							<targetDate>20120930</targetDate>
							<targetValue>5000</targetValue>
							<successIndicator />
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities>
						<activity>
							<action>Identify and contact potential resellers</action>
							<startDate>20120801</startDate>
							<endDate>20120930</endDate>
							<upfrontCost />
							<ongoingCost />
							<order>0</order>
							<ongoingFrequency>3</ongoingFrequency>
							<responsible>New reseller support staff</responsible>
						</activity>
					</activities>
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Develop reseller contracts, policies, support</summary>
					<objectiveType>2</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>3</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Reseller systems in place</summary>
							<targetDate>20121001</targetDate>
							<targetValue />
							<successIndicator />
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities>
						<activity>
							<action>Develop reseller contracts, policies and contracts</action>
							<startDate>20120401</startDate>
							<endDate>20120630</endDate>
							<upfrontCost />
							<ongoingCost />
							<order>0</order>
							<ongoingFrequency>3</ongoingFrequency>
							<responsible>Tom Russell &amp; Melissa Smith </responsible>
						</activity>
					</activities>
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Prepare for revenue ramp</summary>
					<objectiveType>0</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>3</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Number of resellers signed</summary>
							<targetDate>20120930</targetDate>
							<targetValue>4</targetValue>
							<successIndicator />
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities />
				</objective>
			</objectives>
		</theme>
		<theme>
			<title>Mantra Juice buy a hydraulic Juice machine  efficiently produce more juice </title>
			<startDate>20120101</startDate>
			<endDate>20130726</endDate>
			<mandatory>1</mandatory>
			<order>0</order>
			<enhanceCustomerValue>1</enhanceCustomerValue>
			<enhanceUniqueness>1</enhanceUniqueness>
			<expensesOneTime />
			<expensesMonthly />
			<expensesQuarterly />
			<expensesAnnually />
			<revenueMonthly>60000</revenueMonthly>
			<revenueOneTime />
			<revenueQuarterly />
			<revenueAnnually />
			<cogsOneTime />
			<cogsMonthly />
			<cogsQuarterly />
			<cogsAnnually />
			<costsOneTime />
			<costsMonthly>9000</costsMonthly>
			<costsQuarterly />
			<costsAnnually />
			<expensesMonthlyAdjustment />
			<expensesQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<expensesAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<revenueMonthlyAdjustment>30</revenueMonthlyAdjustment>
			<revenueQuarterlyAdjustment>8100</revenueQuarterlyAdjustment>
			<revenueAnnuallyAdjustment>32400</revenueAnnuallyAdjustment>
			<cogsMonthlyAdjustment>9</cogsMonthlyAdjustment>
			<cogsQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<cogsAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<costsMonthlyAdjustment />
			<costsQuarterlyAdjustment />
			<costsAnnuallyAdjustment />
			<responsible>Tom Russell &amp; Melissa Smith </responsible>
			<objectives>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Buy a hydrolic fruit and juice machine</summary>
					<objectiveType>0</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>3</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Number of prospective customers</summary>
							<targetDate>20130326</targetDate>
							<targetValue />
							<successIndicator>1</successIndicator>
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities />
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>More juice and incorperate a juice cleanse during teacher training and workshops</summary>
					<objectiveType>1</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>1</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Cumulative revenue</summary>
							<targetDate>20130326</targetDate>
							<targetValue />
							<successIndicator>0</successIndicator>
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities />
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Add sales support staff</summary>
					<objectiveType>3</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>3</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary>Average number of jobs per customer</summary>
							<targetDate>20130326</targetDate>
							<targetValue />
							<successIndicator>0</successIndicator>
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities />
				</objective>
				<objective>
					<order>0</order>
					<summary>Completed product</summary>
					<objectiveType>2</objectiveType>
					<reviewFrequency>1</reviewFrequency>
					<metrics>
						<metric>
							<summary />
							<targetDate />
							<targetValue />
							<successIndicator>0</successIndicator>
							<measurements />
							<charts />
						</metric>
					</metrics>
					<activities>
						<activity>
							<action>Untitled Activity</action>
							<startDate>20120101</startDate>
							<endDate>20120331</endDate>
							<upfrontCost />
							<ongoingCost />
							<order>0</order>
							<ongoingFrequency>3</ongoingFrequency>
							<responsible>Tom Russell </responsible>
						</activity>
					</activities>
				</objective>
			</objectives>
		</theme>
	</themes>
</stratfile>